Hmm.
The pier found us at the hotel The fortress fell,
the sanctuaries breached A frantic call, a
bug-out plan A safe house just outside her reach
The convoy rolled, the silence set
To hide instead
A childhood room, a tiny space In an accessible,
cramped place The doorway is too narrow I can't
get through the bathroom door Fall upon the
hardwood floor My spirit feeling bruised and
sore It's a hell of inconvenience
A fragile temporary defense But I am safe here,
hiding out I kill the fear, I kill the doubt This
is the blue water bunker
My safe person
You'll see me through
The nights are long, the bed is small I lie awake,
I'm terrified Of what's to come with nowhere
left to hide The cord is looming dark and deep I
cannot rest, I cannot sleep It's a hell of
inconvenience
A fragile temporary defense But I am safe here,
hiding out I kill the fear, I kill the doubt This
is the blue water bunker And I am here with you My
safe person
You'll see me through
But in the dark you take my hand You're the one
who'll understand You and Aubrey here with me My
anchor's in this angry sea The house is small,
the fear is real But your love is what I feel
Safe
In the blue water bunker Safe